carehomemarketeers.co.uk 2016-04-21

# Privacy Policy For The Care Home Marketeers

At Care Home Marketeers, we are dedicated to safeguarding and preserving your privacy when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us. This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you when you are on this site.

We do update this Policy from time to time so please do return and review this Policy regularly.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998, our data controller is Peter Cullen.

## Information We Collect

In operating our website, we may collect and process the following data about you:

· Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.  
· Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you registered for information or make a purchase.  
· Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.  
· We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

## Use of IP Addresses And Cookies

We may on occasion gather information regarding your computer whilst you are on our website.

· This enables us to improve our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers where appropriate.  
· Such information will not identify you personally; it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site.  
· Similarly, to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you.  
· All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser that enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.  
· Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

## Use of Your Information

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

· To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services.  
· To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.  
· To provide information on other products, which we feel, may be of interest to you, where you have consented to receive such information.  
· To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.  
· If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those, which were the subject of a previous sale to you.  
· To speed up your searches.  
· To recognise you when you return to our site.

Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors.

## Storing Your Personal Data

Data that is provided to us is stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety. The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.

## Disclosing Your Information

Where applicable, we may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our subsidiaries, our holding company and its other subsidiaries (if any).  
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

· Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.  
· Where we are legally required to disclose your information.  
· To assist fraud protection and minimise credit risk.

## Third Party Links

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites

## Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. However, we advise that you check this page regularly to keep up to date with any necessary changes.

## Access to Information

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access the information that we hold about you. Please note that any demand for access may be subject to payment of a fee of £10, which covers our costs in providing you with the information requested. Should you wish to receive details that we hold about you please contact us using the contact details below.

Care Home Marketeers, Flook House, Belvedere Road, Taunton, Somerset, TA1 1BT.

## Contact Us

We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://carehomemarketeers.co.uk/contact-us/ "Contact Us")
